<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BookFlip</string>

    <string name="app_text">BOOKFLIP</string>

    <string name="atomic_habits_description">\"Atomic Habits\" is a self-help book written by James Clear, which offers a practical and scientifically-based approach to building good habits and breaking bad ones.\n\nThe book is structured around Clear\'s four-step model for creating lasting habits: cue, craving, response, and reward. He explains how habits are formed, how they can be changed, and how small, incremental improvements can lead to significant long-term changes.\n\nThroughout the book, Clear shares practical strategies for habit formation, including how to create effective cues, how to make habits attractive and rewarding, and how to overcome obstacles and setbacks. He also emphasizes the importance of tracking progress and building a supportive environment to sustain long-term habit change.\n\nOverall, \"Atomic Habits\" is a comprehensive and practical guide to building better habits, backed up by scientific research and real-world examples. The book is aimed at anyone who wants to make positive changes in their life, whether it\'s to improve their health, productivity, relationships, or overall well-being.</string>

    <!-- Ikigai book description -->
    <string name="ikigai_description">\"Ikigai: The Japanese Secret to a Long and Happy Life\" is a non-fiction book written by Héctor García and Francesc Miralles. The book explores the concept of ikigai, which is often translated as \"a reason for being\" or \"a purpose in life.\"\n\nThrough interviews and research, García and Miralles examine how the concept of ikigai has helped the people of Okinawa, Japan, to live longer, healthier, and more fulfilled lives. They also share practical tips for finding one\'s own ikigai, such as identifying one\'s passions, skills, and values.\n\nOverall, \"Ikigai\" offers a thought-provoking and inspiring perspective on how to find meaning and happiness in life, and is recommended for anyone seeking to live a more purposeful and fulfilling life.</string>

    <!-- How to Win Friends and Influence People book description -->
    <string name="how_to_win_friends_description">\"How to Win Friends and Influence People\" is a self-help book written by Dale Carnegie. First published in 1936, the book has sold millions of copies worldwide and is widely regarded as a classic in the genre.\n\nThe book offers practical advice and techniques for improving one\'s communication and interpersonal skills, with the aim of building better relationships and achieving greater success in both personal and professional life. Topics covered in the book include how to make people like you, how to persuade others to your way of thinking, and how to be a better listener.\n\nCarnegie\'s principles are based on human psychology and his own experiences teaching communication and leadership skills to thousands of students. His teachings continue to be relevant today, and the book remains a popular and influential guide for personal and professional development.</string>

    <!-- The Psychology of Money book description -->
    <string name="psychology_of_money_description">\"The Psychology of Money\" is a non-fiction book written by Morgan Housel. The book explores the psychological and behavioral aspects of money and how they shape our attitudes and decisions about wealth.\n\nThrough a series of anecdotes and case studies, Housel illustrates how factors such as our upbringing, social norms, and cognitive biases can influence our financial choices and outcomes. He also discusses the importance of understanding risk and uncertainty, the role of luck in success, and the benefits of long-term thinking.\n\nOverall, \"The Psychology of Money\" is a fascinating and insightful exploration of the intersection between psychology and finance, and is recommended for anyone seeking to improve their financial well-being and gain a deeper understanding of the role money plays in our lives.</string>

    <!-- Rich Dad and Poor Dad -->
    <string name="rich_dad_poor_dad_description">\"Rich Dad, Poor Dad\" is a personal finance book written by Robert Kiyosaki. The book is based on Kiyosaki\'s life experiences and contrasts the financial habits of his \"poor dad\" (his biological father) and his \"rich dad\" (his best friend\'s father).\n\nThrough his storytelling, Kiyosaki shares important lessons about personal finance and wealth creation. He emphasizes the importance of financial education, asset ownership, and passive income, and encourages readers to adopt a \"rich mindset\" in order to achieve financial independence.\n\nOverall, \"Rich Dad, Poor Dad\" is an inspiring and thought-provoking book that challenges conventional ideas about money and encourages readers to take control of their financial futures.</string>
</resources>